难以置信你居然说服我这样干了
I still can't believeyouabctalked me into this.
别这样 亲爱的
Come on, honey.
你要让他泄气了
You're gonna throw him off.
没事 快好了
It's okay. I'm almost done.
臀部再打点光
A little more light on your hips.
天
Oh, god.
为啥在生2个小孩前 你不叫我作裸体画
Why couldn't you have come upabcwith this before I had two kids?
你看上去棒极了
You look amazing.
好 完成了
Okay, I think... yeah, I'm done.
想看看吗?
Wanna come take a look?
我不敢 你先看
I can'T. You first.
不 我们一起来
No, we'll look together.
我不懂了 我以为--
I don't understand.I--Iabcthought--
这是什么鬼?
what the hell is that?
亲爱的 别激动
Honey. It's okay.
这不是我们说好的abc我不会为此付钱
This is not what weabcdiscussed, or what I paid for.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这可是我最好作品之一
I think this is one ofabcthe best I've ever done.
你得退钱
I want my money back.
抱歉 我这可不是百货公司的摄影工作室
I'm sorry,but this is not someabcdepartment store photo studio.
这也不是我妻子
And this is not my wife.
这就是 你要我如实画出她的样子
Yes, it is. You asked me toabcpaint her exactly as she looks.
我就是这么做的
That's exactly what I did.
亲爱的 住手
Honey! Oh, stop it!
怎么了? Brandon!
What's going on? Brandon!
周五前最好把支票寄到我的邮箱里
That check... better beabcin my mailbox by friday.
否则我会回来找你麻烦
Or I'll be back.
我们走!
Come on!
- 怎么了?abc- 不知道
- What happened?abc- I don't know.
他们看到画后就发疯了
They saw the painting andabcthey just freaked out.
这是什么?
Brandon, what is this?
什么这是什么 她的肖像啊
What do you mean? It's her portrait.
有什么不对吗?
What's wrong with it?
这是什么?
Why's this in here?
看第一栏最后一个条目
First column, last entry.
今天天气好晴朗
Today is going to be a good day.
就是他?
This him?
- 是的abc- 不是
- Yes.abc- No.
她是问你就是那个我试图abc利用医疗费用付账的私家侦探
She means are you the private investigator whoseabcbills I've tried to slip through as medical expenses?
我叫Lucas Douglas 私家侦探
I'm lucas douglas, P.I.
医院不请私家侦探作为雇员
This hospital's not putting aabcprivate investigator on retainer.
也不会为假冒维修自动贩卖机abc低温保持器 和电梯买单
Nor is it gonna pay any more phony repairsabcon vending machines, cryostats, or elevators.
信息拯救生命
Information saves lives.
救人等于省钱
Saving lives saves money.
不 救人得花钱abc所以我得确保还有点剩!
No, saving lives costs money, which is why I'mabctrying to make sure there's still some left!
你想请私家侦探
You want your own personal P.I.
那就得私人买单
You're gonna have toabcpay for him yourself.
- 不好意思了abc- 不 我理解
- Sorry.abc- No, I understand.
话说 鞋子好看
Hey, I--I like theabcshoes, by the way.
谢...谢
thank... you.
你才不是喜欢鞋子 你喜欢她的腿
You don't like herabcshoes. You like her legs.
说鞋子好看就没那么变态
It sounds less creepy if you say shoes.
少一分变态 多一分娘
Less creepy, more gay.
这正是我的座右铭
That's my firm's motto.
什么是低温保持器啊?
What is a cryostat?
我也不晓得
No idea.
修了这个的人拿不到钱了
Whoever fixed ours isabcabout to get stiffed.
最近其余的作品都没有视觉扭曲
There's no distorted perspectiveabcin any of his other recent works.
也没那么出色
Not much talent, either.
症状就这么出现了
So the symptoms just came on.
急性发作的视觉失认指向中风或脑瘤
Acute onset visual agnosiaabcpoints to a stroke or brain tumor.
磁共振显示无中风或脑瘤
M.R.I.Revealed no stroke or brain tumor.
应再做一次增强磁共振
We should do another with contrast.
如果他像其他挣扎生存的艺术家一样abc就会吸毒
If he's like the other strugglingabcartists I've known, he's also into drugs.
我们该-- 你看啥?
We should-- whatabcare you looking at?
明显是个笨蛋啊
Apparently a moron.
第一--急诊室常规会查是否吸毒
One--E.R. Routinelyabctests for drugs.
如果有 档案就不会到我们手上了
If it was positive, we wouldn'tabcbe looking at this file.
说你笨的第二原因--abc为车的贷款付12%的利息?
Two--who pays 12%abcinterest on a car loan?
你怎么--是不是查我的信用记录了?
How did you-- did youabcrun a credit check on me?
不...这样犯法了
No... that would be illegal.
可着实有趣abc而且请人去帮我查 又不算...
Interestingly enough, payingabcsomeone to run it for me, though...
怎么了? 这是我的工作
What? It's part of my job.
你的工作是诊断病人
Your job is to diagnose patients.
我跟团队一起干的
Which I do with the team.
要是我不了解一切abc又怎能合理利用团队呢
How am I supposed to know how best to utilizeabcthat team if I don't know everything about them?
话说梵高患有神经性梅毒
Say the van gogh turnsabcout to have neurosyphilis,
我们最后一瓶青霉素在储藏室里
and our last vial ofabcpenicillin is in a storeroom
在天花板2英尺高 20英里长的走廊尽头
at the end of a 20-mile hallwayabcwith a two-foot high ceiling.
你发现我们中有人有abc橡皮人可伸缩的能力?
You've discovered that one of us has been hidingabcthe ability to stretch or shrink themselves?
不 我才不会泄露他人的超能力
No. I would never outabcsomeone's super powers.
不过 这个...
This, on the other hand...
你爬行20英里?
you crawled 20 miles?
我上了吉尼斯记录
My name's in the guinness book.
这肯定让妞们刮目相看啊
I'll bet that reallyabcimpresses the babes.
我不是为妞才这么做的
I didn't do it to get the babes.
对 这样就玷污了你纯洁的出发点
No, that would cheapen theabcpurity of your achievement.
抱歉打断一下abc有个病人可能患有脑癌
sorry to interrupt, but we have aabcpatient with a probable brain tumor.
需要做增强磁共振来确认一下
Who needs an M.R.I.Withabccontrast, we've established that.
查到Taub的什么事?
What do you got on taub?
没查到Taub的什么事
I got nothing on taub.
可能是环境影响abc查查工作室有没有毒素 霉菌和真菌
could also be environmental. We shouldabccheck his studio for toxins, mold, fungus.
不过Taub的老婆倒--
Taub's wife, onabcthe other hand--
House...够了
House... that's enough.
老大说得对 没时间八卦了
Dad's right. This is no time for gossip.
病人急需帮助
A patient desperately needs our help.
查他的脑子和房子
Check his head and his house.
- Lucas不能去吗--abc- 不
- Can't lucas-- abc- nope.
他很忙
He's very busy.
要是有肿瘤的话 测试会看出来--
if there is a tumor,abcthis test will show us--
这东西危险吗?
is that stuff dangerous?
只是造影剂
This is just the contrast material.
有一点过敏反应的风险
There is a small risk ofabcan anaphylactic reaction.
我会因此停止呼吸?
I could stop breathing?
别担心 我们有万全准备了
Don't worry. We're preparedabcto deal with whatever happens.
我今早画了些画 都很正常
You know, I did some drawingsabcthis morning, and they seemed fine.
也许是吃错东西所致吧
So maybe it was just aabcreaction to something I ate.
你认识多少人吃错东西abc会有你这般反应?
How many people you know have reactions likeabcthat to something they ate for breakfast?
要是我好点了--
But if I'mabcgetting better--
你必须持续好转
you will continue to get better.
如果不是 那我们就得知道原因abc这样才能对症下药
If you're not, we need to know why notabcso we can start treatment immediately.
让他们测吧
Baby, let them do the test.
铅中毒会引起视觉失认吗?
Can lead poisoning cause visual agnosia?
除非在血液里验到铅
not without lead showingabcup in the blood work.
医药箱里除了无毒洗漱用品外 无他
Nothing in the medicine cabinetabcexcept some harmless toiletries.
也无霉菌或真菌迹象
No signs of mold orabcfungus anywhere, either.
你觉得House查到你妻子什么了?
You think House reallyabcgot something on your wife?
不 查到了我也不在乎
No. Not that I'd care if he did.
等等 你老婆在床上跟看门人干
Wait, your wife's doingabcthe doorman in your bed,
汗水沾满你花钱买的床单--
and they're sweating all overabcthe sheets that you paid for and--
我妻子没有跟看门人上床
my wife's not doing the doorman.
- 你又知道?abc- 我们没有看门人
- How do you know?abc- We don't have a doorman.
我就是知道 行了吗? 不说这个了
And I just do, okay? Drop it.
大学时 我和朋友想到了一条abc平方反比定律
In college,my friends and i cameabcup with an inverse-square law.
听上去像有趣的一伙人
Sounds likea real fun group.
看上去最内向规矩的那个女孩
The girls who you think are theabcmost inhibited... straight arrows...
往往是最容易上钩那个
they're the ones you hook up with.
你是说我妻子是个荡妇?
Are you saying my wife's a slut?
要是我妻子是个荡妇 我不想被蒙在鼓里
I'm saying if my wife wasabca slut, I'd wanna know.
他住的地方没问题
his place was clean.
脑袋也一样
so is his head.
即使增强了 还是没有肿块和损伤
Even with contrast,noabcmasses, no lesions.
一个无明显神经学原因的神经学症状
A neurological symptom withabcno apparent neurological cause.
发病时程排除了癌症和多发性硬化症
Time course means we canabcrule out cancer and M.S.
只剩毒素和毒品了
Just leaves toxins or drugs.
13说是毒品时你不是叫她笨蛋吗?
You called thirteen a moronabcfor thinking it was drugs.
是啊 那时候她还有其他选择
Yeah, but when she saidabcit,she had other options.
我又很想爆她笨蛋的贷款 还有你--
And I really just wanted to segueabcinto her stupid loan and your--
脑内海绵状血管瘤可能破裂
a cavernous angioma inabcthe brain could leak.
一旦血被吸收 压力降低abc症状就会消失
Once the blood gets reabsorbed, theabcpressure goes down,the symptom goes away.
他绝不会同意岩静脉取样
He'll never consent toabcpetrosal vein sampling.
真的?
Really?
注射显影剂也让他很紧张
He was nervous about anabcinjection of contrast.
他女朋友惹火不?
Is his girlfriend hot?
我不是说发烧abc她是否身材好又漂亮?
And I'm not talking fever here. Iabcmean, is she all curvy and perky?
很惹火 他要是死了abc我们都高兴 但--
Very...and if he dies, it'sabcgood news for all of us, but--
这就解释了为什么他的画这么差
that explains why all his paintings suck.
他到底哪里有毛病了
And what's wrong with him.
你去哪?
Where are you going?
去告诉他可能脑里有个大肿瘤
To tell him he may have aabcmassive brain tumor.
但他没有
But he doesn't.
我知道 我又不笨 是药物
I know. I'm not a moron. It's drugs.
你脑里可能有个大瘤
You seem to have a massive brain tumor.
你是谁?
Who are you?
他是House医生 他很高兴见到你
He's dr. House. He'sabcpleased to meet you.
在你的成像中看不出 所以得把脑袋切开
We found no trace on any of yourabcimaging, so we need to cut your head open.
有风险 不过这是救命的唯一方法
It's risky, but it's theabconly way to save your life.
不
No.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
我不能说不?
I'm not allowed to say no?
你不准这么镇定
You're not allowed to not be terrified.
住院了还这么镇定只有两个原因
There's only two good reasonsabcnot to be terrified in a hospital.
你产生错觉了
You're delusional.
注射显影剂没有让你担心
But then you're not afraid ofabccontrast material either.
除非你知道自己没事
Or you know you're fine.
既然不是我们跟你说的abc就代表你有事隐瞒
Since we haven't told you you're fine, youabcobviously have information we don't have.
你在吃什么药?
What drugs are you on?
他的药检没问题
His drug tests were clean.
药检只能测出他们想测的药
Drug tests only test forabcdrugs they've made tests for.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
辣妹以为他是个伟大的艺术家abc卖画给有钱有品味的人
Hottie thinks that he's a great artist,abcselling art to the rich and tasteful.
她也许不懂艺术abc但银行账户不说谎
She's stupid enough to be fooled by theabccanvases, but bank accounts don't lie.
他需要钱
He needed money.
没有多少工作不费时 无需经验和技巧
There's not many jobs you can do that don'tabcrequire time, training, and intelligence.
我知道你不是新闻主持人和超模abc这些工作不会引起视觉失认
And I know you're not a news anchor or aabcsupermodel, 'cause those jobs seldom cause agnosia.
他是小白鼠
He's a guinea pig.
公司雇他测试未经试验的药
Companies pay him toabctest their untested drugs.
辣妹去尿还是喝咖啡了?
Did hottie go for a pee or coffee?
你最好别费时否认了
Either way,I don't think youabcshould waste any time on denials.
临床试验本应该是安全的
The clinical trials wereabcsupposed to be safe.
那些药就要被药监局批准了
The drugs are about toabcbe approved by the fda.
那些药? 你参加了几次试验?
Drugs? How many trials are you on?
3次
Three.
佩服
Admirable.
没几个笨蛋有这种勇气
Not many idiots have that much ambition.
入院后症状就消失了abc所服的药应该已被系统清除了
You've been symptom-free since your admission, soabcwhatever you took has probably cleared your system now.
你会好起来的
You'll be fine.
留院观察一晚以确保没事abc查出试验的药物
Keep him overnight,just to make sure, andabcget the names of all the trials he's been in.
你会告诉Heather吗?
You gonna tell heather?
不会 即使我关心你们也很想说
Couldn't, even if Iabccared enough to want to.
不错嘛
Not bad.
差点忍过一天了
You almost made it the whole day.
你查出什么了?
What'd you find out?
我想看看大家的反应
The point is to see how everyone reacts.
我去把他们叫来
I'm gonna go get the rest of the gang.
少废话 House
Cut the crap, House.
你老婆开了个人名义的银行户头
Your wife has a separate bankabcaccount in her name only.
一年来她每周定期存现金
She's been making weekly cashabcdeposits for about a year now.
迄今...从没取过款
No withdrawals... yet.
就这样? 一个银行账户?
That's it? A bank account?
一个秘密银行账户
A secret bank account.
你凭什么觉得那是个"秘密"账户呢?
What makes you think it's a secret?
因为要不是个秘密 你会说那个账户abc而不是一个账户
Because if it wasn't, you'dabccall it "the" bank account.
该死
Damn.
撒谎的时候老是用错冠词
Always forget to use theabcright article when lying.
那不是秘密的
It's not secret.
我们在更新家具
We're refurnishing.
我们做了预算 开了个账户
We set the budget,set up an account.
开户那天我太忙了过不去
I just couldn't make it toabcthe bank the day we opened it.
你们要花10万买家具?
You're spendingabcalmost $100,000 on furniture?
是的
Yes.
- 怎么了?abc- 我不知道
- What happened?abc- I don't know.
他本来好好的 突然癫痫发作
He was fine, then all of aabcsudden, he started seizing.
他告诉我说他好多了
He said you told him he was better.
到底怎么了? 他到底怎么了?
What's happening? What's wrong with him?
她很辣啊
She is hot.
显然药物还未清除出体内
Obviously the drugs weren'tabcout of his system.
他用的药物不可能导致癫痫发作
None of these drugs, nor the drugs that they'reabcderived from, are known for causing seizures.
药物本身不会引发
By themselves, no.
但是三种未经检测核准的药物就说不好了
But three unproven,untested drugs?
就像那样abc(70年代电视剧)
This is like the mod squad.
没有人能阻止他们
No one could stop them.
太荒谬了 竟然用钱abc让人们服用有潜在危险的药
Ridiculous that they let people takeabcpotentially dangerous drugs for money.
长话短说
Just to short circuit that discussion,
走投无路的人不应该进行临床药物试验
people should not be testing drugsabcbecause they're desperate.
但人要不是走投无路abc怎会去接受临床药物试验
But people won't testabcdrugs unless they're desperate.
我们需要新药救孩子跟小狗
We need drugs to saveabcchildren and puppies.
所以我们需要走投无路的人
Ergo, we need desperate people.
所以医疗福利谋杀了孩子们
Ergo, welfare kills sick children.
第一个药--
Firstabcdrug--
叫双性恋药怎么样?
why don't we call it bisexidrine?
临床试验包涵了实验阶段的药物
Clinical trials involveabcexperimental drugs.
意味着它们还没有好听又好记的名字
Means they don'tabchave comforting, catchy names yet.
只有随机又难记的号码
Just random, unmemorable trial numbers.
继续
Go ahead.
双性恋药设计为抗凝药
Bisexidrine is designed asabcan anticoagulant.
显示可导致恶心 勃起障碍 失眠的风险
Phase one indicated some riskabcof nausea, E.D., And insomnia.
第二种药
Second drug.
通奸药
Cuckoldisol.
- 她有外遇?abc- 更糟
- She is having an affair?abc- Worse.
性用荷尔蒙和情感来解释
Sex can be dismissed asabchormonal or emotional.
更容易被原谅
Can be easily regretted.
但是钱是有计划性的决定
Money is always a calculated decision.
我老婆有自己的银行账户abcHouse以为我不知道
My wife has her own bank accountabcthat House doesn't think I know about.
震惊啊  继续说
Shocking. Discuss.
第二个药用于自身免疫疗法abc几乎没有副作用
Drug b is an autoimmuneabctreatment. Almost no side effects.
就算这个药物效用符合预期
But even if it's doing whatabcit's supposed to be doing,
也与抗凝剂和抗癫痫药不相容
it doesn't mix well withabcanticoagulants or anticonvulsives.
第三个药是什么?
which is the third drug?
超级膝盖酸软药
World's-sorest-knees-isil.
顺便说一句 那一直是Cuddy的外号
Cuddy used to have thatabctitle, by the way.
如果药物正常作用的话abc有一百万种相互作用的可能性
there's a million ways these drugs could interactabcif they're doing what they're supposed to.
如果没正常作用 两百万种的可能
If they're not,two million.
找出到底是哪种导致了病人的症状abc会非常有意思
And it'd be interesting to know which ofabcthose interactions was causing the problem.
不幸的是 我们没必要这么干
Unfortunately,we don't have to.
我们只要停止这个相互作用就行了
We just have to stop the interacting.
- 要是不知道是哪种...abc- 那就都停了
- If we don't knowabcwhich-- - stop them all.
给他做透析 清理他的全身
Put him on dialysis.abcClear out his system.
快速解毒的风险有心律失常abc再次诱发癫痫 肝衰竭
Rapid detoxrisks arrhythmia,abcanother seizure,hepatic failure.
不同之处在于 我们知道风险在哪儿
Difference is, weabcknow what those risks are.
给他做透析
Put him on dialysis.
肾衰竭才做透析 是吗?
Dialysis. Use that forabckidney failure,right?
别担心 你的肾没事
Don't worry. Your kidneys are fine.
他不是担心他的肾
He's not worried about his kidneys.
他是担心怎么跟女朋友解释
He's worried about how he's going toabcexplain the dialysis to his girlfriend.
我不想她担心
I just don't want her to worry.
你是不想她离开你吧?
You mean you don't want her to leave you?
这又怎么了? 我爱她
What's wrong with that? I love her.
我并不是惯于欺骗她
It's not like I've lied toabcher about anything important.
我是个画家
I am an artist.
我过去卖了很多画 只是...
I've sold plenty of paintingsabcin the past. It's just...
最近没怎么卖出去而已
I've hit a bit of a dryabcspell lately, is all.
那就告诉她
So tell her that.
他做不到
He can't.
他想让她也快乐
He wants her to be happy too.
他只说她想听的
He's telling her what she wants to hear.
你不知道
You didn't know?
不知道
No.
你要怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
她没跟别人睡 她没赌钱输光
She's not sleeping around.abcShe's not gambling it away.
她甚至一个子儿都没动过
She hasn't even spent any of it.
所以我没理由去做什么
So I don't see a reason to do anything.
你不觉得谈谈也许--
You don't think aabcconversation might--
你知道有多少人abc对他们的感情生活完全幸福和满意?
how many people do you know in completelyabchappy and fulfilled relationships?
- 没有abc- 我就是
- None.abc- I am.
大多数人都按照故事书来定义感情
Most people cling to some story bookabcnotion of what a relationship is.
你不能有不完美的想法
You can't have an imperfect thought.
你不能有私人空间abc你不能...
You can't have aabcprivate zone.You can't--
把钱藏起来 存到一个秘密账户里?
steal money and hide itabcaway in a secret account?
她让我开心 我让她开心 就足够了
She makes me happy. Iabcmake her happy. It works.
因为我们不是故事书
Because we don't do storybook.
我也不打算干涉她的事
And I don't plan toabcpoke into her business.
你透析的想法是对的
You were right about the dialysis.
他一整夜都没有癫痫发作和视觉症状
He made it through the night withoutabcany more seizures or visual symptoms.
等我吃完早饭 到了办公室 我仍是对的
And I am going to be just as rightabcafter breakfast up in my office.
区别在于 那时有其他人在场
The only difference is I'm gonnaabcbe right in front of other people.
也就是说你在这儿谈 不是要说医学问题
Which means you're not here toabctalk about the medicine.
工作上你怎么折腾我都行abc只是不要干涉我的私生活
You can screw with me all you want atabcwork, but stay out of my personal life.
她怎么说?
What did she say?
你听没听到我刚才说的?
Did you just hear what I said?
我只听到了"工作上你怎么折腾我都行"
I heard the part about you canabcscrew with me at work all you want.
- 想听听建议?abc- 当然不想
- Want my advice?abc- Of course not.
好 正好我也不清楚你该怎么做
Good, 'cause I have noabcidea what you should do.
我只知道你下一步会干什么
I only know what you're going to do.
- 你会去...abc- 我说了不想听建议
- You're gonna-- - I saidabcI didn't want your advice.
我说了这不是个建议
I said this is not advice.
你会原谅她私开账户
You are going to forgiveabcher for opening that account,
并且你招供你所做过的事
and you're going toabcconfess everything you've done,
然后祈求她的原谅
and then you're gonnaabcbeg her to forgive you.
这样做有什么好处?
What purpose could that possibly serve?
没有 我没说你应该这么做abc但是你会这么做
None... which is why I'm notabcsaying you should. But you will.
你的终极战是?
what's your end game?
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
在过道里
At the track.
那有...六英里远
That's, like, six miles away.
这玩意儿真酷
How cool are these things?
我觉得像傻子
I feel like an idiot.
我不会再给你我的任何东西
I'm not giving you any more of my stuff.
你有夜视镜吗?
You have those night vision goggles?
没有
No.
你说谎
You're lying.
你喜欢把他弄得一团糟
You like making him miserable.
你喜欢让人们远离你
You like driving people away from you.
他应当知道真相
He deserved to know the truth.
你不去挖掘 哪来的真相
There was no truth until you dug it up.
可你能感觉到有些事存在abc即使看不见 不是吗
You do know that stuff existsabceven when you can't see it, right?
这个真相跟他有关 也跟她有关
It was a truth that mattered to himabcand a truth that mattered to her.
但跟你有什么关系?
Why did it matter to you?
首先 不要说"这个真相"
first of all, stop saying "a" truth.
真相只有一个
There is only one truth.
对你而言也许是
That may be true for you.
悲惨的人能拯救更多的生命
Miserable people save more lives.
如果你的生活很有意义abc你的工作就没必要有意义了
If your life has meaning, yourabcjob doesn't have to have meaning.
悲惨的人总是期待能有个让他痛哭的怀抱
Screw-ups are more palatable if youabchave someone's arms to go cry in.
有点道理
Yeah, that makes sense.
通常这个问题会引起争论
Usually I have moreabcof a fight on that one.
那你为什么要把Taub整得很悲惨?
So why are you making taub miserable?
我刚说过!
I just said!
他为了拯救婚姻辞了上一个工作
He left his last jobabcto save his marriage.
你觉得他婚姻要是完了abc他会更努力地为你工作?
If his marriage falls apart, youabcthink he'll be working harder for you?
或者他再也不会为你工作了?
Or you think he won'tabcbe working for you at all?
他的头颈部全肿了
his head and neck areabccompletely swollen.
我需要气管插管包 他的咽喉正在闭死
I need a trache kit.abcHis throat's closing.
找不到任何体表标志
Can't find any landmarks.
直接切
Just start cutting.
气管插管?
An exploratory trache?
没别的办法
We don't have a choice.
好了
Got it.
他脸肿得挤闭了泪腺
his face is so swollen itabcsqueezed his tear ducts shut.
只能手动润滑他的眼球
We've been lubricating his eyes by hand.
给了类固醇激素静点和药膏来减轻水肿abc但是作用有限
We started him on steroids,iv and cream, toabcreduce the swelling, but it's having limited effect.
血栓和查加斯寄生虫阴性
Negative for thrombosis and chagas.
可能是感染
Could be infection.
细胞培养还是阴性
Culture's still negative.
会不会免疫系统过度激化abc导致细胞激素风暴
Could be his immune system's onabchyperdrive. Cytokine storm.
为什么你办了三年的健身会员卡abc却只去过两次?
Why would you pay for a three-yearabcgym membership and only go twice?
不好意思 你们还在病例讨论?
Sorry. You guys still diagnosing?
我以为几小时以前就结束了
Thought we'd finished hours ago.
记不记得 我们曾认为病因是abc未经证明批准的鸡尾酒疗法
You remember, when we decided it was the unproven,abcunapproved cocktail of drugs he's been downing like...
他像喝鸡尾酒一样服下
like a cocktail.
他刚刚完成了全血透析
He just completed a total dialysis.
要是药物的原因 他会好多了才对
If it was the drugs,he'd be better.
或是更糟
Or he'd be worse.
你们肯定都没看过电影
I take it none of you saw trainspotting.
你觉得水肿是停药后的反应?
You think swelling is aabcsymptom of withdrawal?
你觉得停药后接连出现三个新症状是巧合?
You think it's a coincidence that three newabcsymptoms cropped up as soon as we took him off the drugs?
可能其中某些症状...
It's possible someabcof the symptoms--
药物或者是答案 或者是巧合
either the drugs are the answer,abcor the drugs are a coincidence.
若是药物引起的 要想更好的解毒方法
If it's one, we have toabcfind a better way to detox him.
若两种可能都存在abc下诊断前 得要找出哪些是停药反应
If it's two, we have to know which symptoms areabcwithdrawal-related before we can formulate a diagnosis.
还是得找更好的办法来解毒
Which means we have to find aabcbetter way to detox him.
那怎么办?
So how do we do it?
再给他用药
Hair of the drug that bit him.
不可能 要是这些药引起的话abc这些药很危险 已经导致...
That's ridiculous. If it is the drugs,they'reabcdangerous, and they've already caused--
所以要给他重新用那些药abc再慢慢断掉
that's why we're gonna put him back onabcthe drugs, and then wean him off again.
但速度要慢
Just much slower.
为什么你们都看他?
Why are you looking at him?
试试吧
Try it out.
老板发话啦! 行动!
You heard the boss! Go!
- Taubabc- 我没跟她谈
- Taub--abc - I didn't talk to her.
- 为什么你...abc- 怎么了
- Why are you--abc- excuse me.
呃 对不起
Uh, sorry.
他挺像我的 是吧
He does look like me,doesn't he?
你把你的帽子给了他
You gave him your hat.
我需要你出去一会儿abc我就能检查你的桌子了
I needed you out of here,soabcI could go through your desk.
当然
Of course.
衬衣真好看
Nice blouse.
这个颜色很衬你 我喜欢
I really like that color on you.
告诉House 要是他想知道我在干什么abc只需要...
Tell House that if he wants to knowabcwhat I'm doing, all he has to do--
不是House 是我
it's not House,abcit's--it's me.
我...我不知道
I was--Iabcdon't know.
我想我们一起喝一杯什么
I was thinking maybe we could getabctogether for a drink or something.
我不太清楚你喜欢什么
I wasn't sure exactly whatabcyou like to do.
- 所以我想...abc- 你监视我？
- So I thought...abc- you'd spy on me.
不 不是监视 更像是研究
No. No. Not spying. More like research.
我觉得在约女人出去之前abc先对她稍作了解总没坏处
I think it's a good idea to get to know a littleabcbit more about a woman before you ask her out.
让她知道你在乎的不仅仅是她的外表
Show you care about more thanabcjust what she looks like.
尽管被你说得天花乱坠abc但你所谓关心的行为...
As romantic as you make that sound, I'mabcpretty sure that what you're doing is...
根本与变态无异
not so much caring as creepy.
这评价不公平
That's not fair.
你在翻我的抽屉
You were scrounging through my desk.
我能翻出什么来?
What the hell am I gonna find out?
你去了密歇根
You went to michigan.
你喜欢在三明治里放一点蛋黄酱
You like your sandwiches aabclittle light on mayo.
你和令堂一直保持联系
You stay in touch with your mother.
你租了abc向"大赦国际"捐款
You rented the english patient andabcyou gave money to amnesty international.
从这儿翻出来abc都是能在搭电梯时和同事聊上的
There's not one thing I can find out in here that youabcwouldn't tell a coworker while riding in an elevator.
我不是变态abc我只是对你感兴趣
I'm not a creep. I justabcthought you seemed interesting.
我闪人了
I'll go now.
对了 这个 呃...
Yeah, these, um...
我把House的糗事爆给你
I'll give you embarrassing info on House.
- 来交换--abc- 不 不必用约会交换
- In exchange for-- -abcno, no need for a date.
只要你雇用我 我会用全部时间abc来追问你关于你的一切
You'd be employing me, so I'd have all theabctime in the world to ask you all about you,
这也将从变态的偷窥abc变成正常的社会交往
and it would fall under the category ofabcsocializing instead of creepy stalking.
那我还得发你工钱?
And I'd be paying you?
我知道有点怪
I know it's weird.
但你付钱让我调查你--这多酷啊
But if you pay me while I checkabcyou out, it's--it's all cool.
而你也会有回报abc你抓住House的把柄
And you get value,youabcget leverage against him.
就能让他守规矩了
Help you keep him in line.
你以为我要别人帮忙abc才能让House守规矩?
You think I needabchelp keeping House in line?
不
No.
不用 对不起
Nope. Sorry.
- 医院负担不起--abc- 你想付多少都行
- This hospital can't afford--abc- oh, whatever you can afford.
你怎么知道我喜欢玫瑰?
How'd you know I liked roses?
我昨晚去你家了
I was in your House last night.
不! 开玩笑
No! I'm kidding.
谁不喜欢玫瑰呢?
Who the hell doesn't like roses?
忘了告诉你
I forgot to tell you.
帕克四重奏要在图书馆筹款活动上演出
The parker quartet's gonnaabcplay at the library fund raiser.
就这样了?
That's it?
是你想到的
It was your idea.
一定会很精彩
They'll be great.
你怎么了?
You okay?
我找不到开信刀
I couldn't find the letter opener.
于是去你的抽屉里找
I went through some of the drawersabcin your desk looking for it.
里面有一叠杰佛逊互助银行的账单
There were a bunch of statementsabcin there from jefferson mutual.
差点就成功了
I was so close.
成功什么?
To what?
你在一个秘密账户里存了83,000
You've got $83,000 sockedabcaway in a secret account.
现在没有了
Not anymore.
我本来想给你一个惊喜 但是...
I wanted to keep it a surprise, but...
我给你买了辆车子
I bought you a car.
那辆...我...
the one that... that I...
我知道你自己绝不会去买 所以...
I knew you would never buyabcit yourself, so...
我一直在存钱
I've been saving.
车子星期五就要送来了
And it's gonna be delivered on friday.
你太好了
You are amazing.
你走运了
Lucky you.
我们在逐渐降低你的剂量
We've gradually reduced your dosage.
实际已经不在用药了
You're actually drug-free now.
我感觉很好 谢谢你
I feel great. Thanks to you.
这是我的职责
All part of the job.
你的血压正常了abc能坐起来吗?
Your blood pressure's normal.abcCan you sit up?
你想干什么--
What areabcyou--ohh!
他的脸怎么了?
What happened to his face?
应该问他的荷尔蒙怎么了abc拿个冰袋来
Question is whatabchappened to his hormones?
这下可以排除试验药物了
we can rule out theabcclinical trial drugs at this point.
他的身体被彻底清洗了两遍
His system hasabcbeen completely cleaned twice.
除非药物在楼梯底下躲起来了
Unless the drugs found aabchiding place under the stairs.
药物可能会引起潜伏的神经病变
Drugs could have set off aabcdormant neurological condition.
说得对
Good point.
坦白也会带来伤害
Coming clean can cause a lot of damage.
譬如疏远 离婚
Alienation, divorce.
我老婆给我买了辆车子
My wife's buying me a car.
我说的是病人
I was talking about the patient.
- 你错了abc- 离婚只是个比喻
- You were wrong.abc- Divorce was metaphorical.
会不会是Kluver-Bucy综合症?
what about kluver-bucy syndrome?
双侧颞叶损伤
Bilateral lesions in the temporal lobes,
主要症状为视觉失认和性欲高涨
visual agnosia and hyper-sexualityabcare the key symptoms.
幸好他有个女友
Good thing he's got that girlfriend.
如果是Kluver-Bucy 他的大脑会短路abc甚至会吞掉自己双手
If it's kluver-bucy,his brain'll meltabcdown, he'll try to swallow his own hands,
那她就可以照顾他形同废人的余生了
and she can take care of him forabcthe rest of his talentless life.
你欠我一个道歉
You owe me an apology.
你为干涉我私生活编出的理据都不成立abc因为她有正当理由--
Any rationalization you had for meddling in myabcprivate life disappeared when she had good reason--
你说的没错
you're right.
我那套用不上了
Fact is,nothing I said applies.
你无需原谅她
You had no reason to forgive her.
也失去了让她原谅你的理由
Therefore, no reason to seek forgiveness.
失去了当傻瓜的理由
No reason to be an idiot.
Kluver-Bucy不能解释癫痫和细胞激素风暴
Kluver-bucy wouldn't explain theabcseizure or the cytokine storm.
断药反应
Withdrawal complications.
而且 她送给你一份abc你自觉不配拥有的大礼物
Then again, she is handing you a giantabcgift that you don't think you deserve.
核磁共振结果显示
The fact that the M.R.I.Showed
双侧颞叶没有损伤 排除了你的理论
no lesions on the temporal lobe tends to ruleabcout your lesions on the temporal lobe theory.
可能是循环问题 而是不是结构性损伤
The damage can be a circulatoryabcissue rather than structural.
核磁共振看不出来
We wouldn't see that on the M.R.I.
Foreman说得对
Foreman's right.
给你老婆打个电话abc告诉她你今晚不回去
Go call your wife, tellabcher you're not coming home
因为你要为病人做一个头部血管造影
'cause you have to give theabcpatient a cranial M.R.Angiogram.
然后道晚安 挂电话
Then say good night and hang up.
怪了 一个不能跑步的人abc却有这么多双跑鞋
Odd that a man who can't run wouldabcown so many pairs of sneakers.
你忙完了能不能把这个挂起来?
You mind hanging thisabcup when you're done?
我一定得找出你的糗事
I have to findabcsomething embarrassing about you.
你不必这么干
No, you don't.
我叫了印度菜
I ordered us indian.
也不必很糗 但要可信
Not too embarrassing,abcjust something credible.
如果你这样交差...
Well, if you hand her that...
她会觉得不需要你
she's not gonna need you anymore.
要是我没东西交差abc她会觉得我很无能
Well, if I don't hand her anything,abcshe'll think I'm incompetent.
我不在乎她是否觉得你无能
I don't care if sheabcthinks you're incompetent.
这招不管用
This isn't gonna work.
目前已经管用了
It's worked so far.
不 我不会撒谎
No, I'm no good at lying.
这我知道
I know.
所以你的掩护是你想干她
That's why your cover isabcthat you want to do her.
我喜欢她 我不想干她
I like her. I don't wanna do her.
那喜欢她还有什么意义?
Then what's the point of liking her?
我意思是 我不仅仅想干她abc我喜欢她
I meant I don't just wantabcto do her. I like her.
你想知道她什么秘密?
What do you think you'reabcgonna find out about her?
一些...私事 一些糗事
Something... personal.abcSomething embarrassing.
我半辈子都花在和这个女人谈判上
I've spent half myabclife negotiating with that woman.
反正是可以逼她向我妥协的事
Anything I can use toabcscare her into saying yes.
没问题
Okay.
没问题?
Okay?
你答应收双倍工钱去威胁他人?
You're okay with being paidabctwice to facilitate blackmail?
我没问题 虽然信不过你abc但没问题
I'm okay. I don'tabcbelieve you,but I'm okay.
你这么做的动机和我一样
You're doing this for theabcsame reason I'm doing this.
看我们谁先达到目的
We'll see who gets there first.
这儿 韦利斯动脉环abc血管缩窄
here it is. Circle ofabcwillis, the vessels are narrow.
对你来说窄了 对他却是正常的
Narrow for you, normal for him.
如果是血管的问题abc他早就出现症状了
If there were problems with theabcvessels, he'd have had symptoms long ago.
如果有别的出现病变 就不一样了
Not if something else changed.
- 比如说?abc- 他的心脏
- Like?abc- His heart.
他最近可能出现过间歇性心律失常
He could have recently gotten anabcintermittent arrhythmia.
我知道心脏(heart)和abc头(head)前仨字母一样
I know "heart" and "head"abcstart with the same three letters,
你得把整个单词念完才行
but you gotta read allabcthe way to the end.
试验性药物导致心律失常 引发低血压
The experimental drug is causingabcarrhythmia,which causes low blood pressure.
结合血管缩窄来看 脑部供血不足
Combine that with those narrow vessels,abcthe brain doesn't get enough blood.
引发了他的全部症状
That causes all of his symptoms.
如果可以诱发心律失常并定位
If we can trigger theabcarrhythmia and identify it,
也许可以阻止他被杀死
we might be able to stopabcit from killing him.
回过家了?
Been home?
没有
No.
做个电生理检测abc找出心律失常的原因
Good. Do an E.P. Study.abcFind the arrhythmia.
我们要将三根电极导管插入你的心脏
We're gonna insert threeabcelectrocatheters into your heart.
告诉Hadley医生 我很抱歉
Tell dr. Hadley I'm sorry.
她能理解
She understands.
你应该亲口对她说
And you should tell her yourself.
- 也许我应该告诉Heather--abc- 你会没事的
- Maybe I should tell heatherabcabout-- - you're gonna be fine.
她那么支持我 人又好abc我却欺骗了她
She's just so supportive. Andabcso great. All I do is lie to her.
要是你告诉她会怎么样?
What happens if you tell her?
我不知道
I don't know.
你爱她 对吧?
You love her, right?
胜过一切 而且她也爱我
More than anything,and she loves me.
如果你开口告诉她abc只会有两个结果
If you open your mouth,oneabcof two things happens.
她要么原谅你 要么离你而去
She either forgivesabcyou or she leaves you.
如果是好的结果 就和现在一样
At best, you wind upabcexactly where you are right now.
坦白是一种美德
It's noble to want to confess.
真的
Really, it is.
但如果带来的是伤害和痛苦abc就不再是美德了
But if the result's just damageabcand pain, that's not noble.
而是自私
That's selfish.
刺激右心房
stimulate right atrium.
没有传导
No more conduction.
你打算什么时候才让我回家?
How long you plan onabckeeping me from going home?
直至你相信我不会干出蠢事来?
Until you're convinced I'm a differentabcperson, one who won't do anything stupid?
内疚很快会消失
Guilt fades quickly.
到星期三 你就想开了
By wednesday, you'll be fine.
右心室
Right ventricle.
你为什么希望它消失?abc你为什么突然关心起我的婚姻来?
And why do you want it to fade? Whyabcdo you suddenly care about my marriage?
因为...如果你的婚姻不破灭--
Because...ifabcit ain't broke--
显然你觉得它已经破灭了--
you obviously think it is broke.
显然你觉得没有
You obviously think it ain't.
你的婚姻好比坏掉的烤面包机
Your marriage is like a broken toaster.
跳出来的是生面包abc你却管它叫烤土司
The bread keeps popping out,andabcyou keep calling it toast.
这很怪 因为你把面包放到过别的烤箱里
Which is weird,because you've putabcyour bread in a lot of toasters.
但显然 你看不出两者间的区别
And apparently,youabcdon't see any difference.
这很有意思
It's kind of fascinating.
他室颤了
He's going into v-tach.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
好消息是--测试奏效了
Good news--theabctest is working.
你的心脏快要爆了abc但最酷的是 你还醒着
Your heart's freaking out, but it'sabccool that you're still conscious.
加大电流
Try to overdrive.
不起作用
Didn't work.
可能会有点灼痛abc充电到60焦 让开
this might burn a littleabcbit. Charging to 60. Clear.
再来一次 充到120焦
Going again,charging to 120.
你染过发了?
Are you dyeing your hair?
- 没有abc- House 让开
- No.abc- House, clear.
好的
Right.
发根变红了
The hair is growing in red.
心律稳定下来了
his heart rate is stabilized.
你的理论是否包括基因变异abc可以解释他的头发变色?
Does your theory include any genetic mutationsabcthat could cause his hair to change color?
要么他谎称自己没有染发
Either he's lying about dyeing...
要么...他快要死了
or just... dying.
头发变红说明不是Kluver-Bucy综合症
red hair means it's not kluver-bucy.
黑色素影响头发的颜色
Melanin affects hair color.
什么会影响黑色素?
What affects melanin?
- 荷尔蒙abc- 荷尔蒙测试正常
- Hormones.abc- Hormone panels were all normal.
年龄
Age.
而头发变亮红?
He's turning prematurely crimson?
遗传障碍
A genetic disorder.
瓦登伯格综合症abc引起心律失常和头发变色
Waardenburg syndrome causesabcarrhythmias and can change hair color.
还有失聪 下一个
And make you deaf. Next.
发现长QT间期
Found a long qt interval.
我想是romano-ward综合症
I think it's romano-ward syndrome.
解释了心律不规则
Explains the irregular heart rhythms.
但不能解释姜汁饼似的发色
But not the ginger nut.
如果是romano-wardabc他身上至少有5处基因变异
If he's got romano's, he's gotabcat least five gene mutations.
头发变红是因为别的病症也不足为奇
Not a big leap to think he hasabcothers that would give him the hair.
死亡可能不期而至
It also gives him the likelihoodabcof sudden and unexpected death.
β-受体阻断剂不正常工作
Beta blockers don't work.
他的心脏负荷不了植入式复律除颤器.
His heart can't handle an I.C.D.
Pete best
Pete best.
天哪
Good god!
就没人读历史么?
Has none of you ever read a history book?
他是甲壳虫乐队本来的鼓手
The original beatles drummer.
一束神经控制心脏的节奏
A bunch of nerves controlsabcthe tempo of the heart.
在合奏中 只要有一个家伙乱了阵脚
They're all playing in time,abcexcept one dude can't keep the beat.
整体就被破坏了
Wrecks the whole thing.
所以后来请了Ringo当鼓手
So we hire ringo.
Pete best 也是个伟大的鼓手
Pete best was actually a great drummer,
但我猜 你的意思是abc需要做心脏交感神经切除术
but I assume you mean the patientabcneeds a cardiac sympathectomy?
也许我该这么直接说吧
Probably should have just said that, huh?
切除神经 他的吞咽 声带和发汗功能abc会有扰乱的风险
Start cutting nerves,you risk hisabcswallowing, vocal cords, sweating.
他可以不用去K歌 不用买止汗露abc省一大笔钱
So he saves a fortune onabckaraoke machines and deodorant.
你觉得他的状况适宜做手术?
You think he's stable enough for surgery?
如果他状况稳定 根本不需手术
If he was,he wouldn't need it.
是啊
Yeah.
你有兄弟姐妹么?
Do you have any brothers and sisters?
一个妹妹
One sister.
他告诉我 他打曲棍球
He told me he was on the lacrosse team.
在高中打 上了大学abc他就给曲棍球队当啦啦队
In high school. In college, he justabccheered the lacrosse team on to victory.
是啊
Yeah.
你和爸爸的关系怎样?
How was your relationship with your dad?
不错 你还能问三个问题
Fine. You have three more questions.
- 你和妈妈的关系怎样?abc- 不错
- How was your relationship with your mom?abc- Fine.
你什么时候失贞?
When did you lose your virginity?
我可不会在电梯里和同事讨论这个
Not something I'd discussabcwith coworkers in an elevator.
还有
And...
还有...
and...
你知道的 是吧?
you know, don't you?
第三个问题有点浪费了
A bit of a wasted third question.
因为回答是"知道什么?"
'Cause the answer is "know what?"
听我多说几句
Okay, bear with me here.
有些人认为我的思维逻辑很复杂
Because some people sometimes considerabcmy thought processes complicated.
我喜欢你 因为你辣 聪明
I'm into you,'causeabcyou're hot. And smart.
顺序如上 但两者都不可缺
In that order,but both are needed.
照片可以修改
Photos can be retouched.
House又是个邪神abc照片就很值得怀疑
And House is an evil genius,abcwhich makes this photo suspicious.
你却不疑心
And yet you're not suspicious.
要么你不够聪明 所以不怀疑abc这样的话
Which means either you're not smartabcenough to be suspicious, in which case,
我对你的兴趣就没那么大了abc或者 你不怀疑
I am less interested inabcyou, or you're not suspicious
因为你知道这是伪造的照片
because you know this isabcactually a doctored photo of House.
那样的话 我对你的兴趣就更大了
In which case,I amabcmore interested in you.
但如此一来 我就白折腾了abc因为你知道我和House在玩你 我就没戏了
But I am wasting my time,because you know thisabcis a game we are playing on you, and I am busted.
出局了
And I'm screwed.
我知道照片是假的
I know the photo's a fake.
知道这是个游戏
And I know this is a game.
对不起
I'm sorry.
太糟了
Too bad.
再见
Good-bye.
既然你知道 我不会给你有价值的东西
So you knew that I wasn't gonnaabcgive you anything worthwhile?
你也不准备回馈我什么
A-and you were never gonna giveabcme anything worthwhile.
那你为什么还要来见我
Then why did youabcbother coming out with me?
我想和House对着干
I... wanted to screw with House.
和我出来就能?
By wasting my time?
讲不通
That doesn't make sense.
不...
No, uh...
一定有另外的理由
there must be another reason.
我再坐回来行吗?
Is it okay if I sit back down here?
你的心率失控
your heartbeat's out of control.
需要做手术 切除心脏和大脑的联系
We need to surgically sever theabcconnection between your heart and brain.
这是必须的 但你得知道后果
We believe it's necessary, butabcyou need to know the ramifications.
你感受不到心绞痛
You'll never be able to feel angina.
所以意识不到自己心脏病发
You may not know if youabchave a heart attack.
可能得不到及时的救治
You may not be able to get help in time.
我平时的医生呢?
Where are my regular doctors?
平时的医生?
Regular doctors?
Taub医生和Hadley医生
Dr. Taub and dr. Hadley.
为什么不是他们来告诉我?
Why aren't they telling me this?
Brandon 我是Hadley医生abc这是Taub医生
Brandon, I am dr. Hadley.abcAnd this is dr. Taub.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
这辈子我都没见过你们
I've never seen you before in my life.
不能做手术
we can't do the surgery.
又回到起点 视觉失认
We're back to where weabcstarted. Visual agnosia.
需要重新检查神经系统疾病
We need toabcreexamine neurological disorders.
病情在缓慢发展
Something's slowly progressing.
不是发展 是一会儿有abc一会没有
This isn't progressing. It'sabcthere, then it's not,then it is.
间歇性出现的新症状
It's a new symptom,intermittence.
不相关
It's irrelevant.
新症状怎么不相关?
Since when is a new symptom irrelevant?
因为是同一个疾病引起的
Since it points towards the same disease.
间歇性符合romano-ward综合症的特点
Intermittence can fit with romano-ward.
仍需要做交感神经切除术
We still need to do a sympathectomy.
也许漏掉了什么
maybe we missed something.
- 毒素abc- 怎么会?
- Toxins.abc- When?
你们检查了所有瓶子 管子 颜料abc还给他脱毒了两次
When you checked every bottle, every can,everyabctube of paint? Or when you detoxed him twice?
也许有毒的颜料他在几个月前用完了
Maybe there is a batch of toxic paintabcthat he used up a few months ago.
那他该在几个月前病倒 而不是现在
Then he would have been sickabcmonths ago, not now.
他住院后体重减轻了
He's lost weight since he got here.
这是他喉咙吸不进空气abc还硬往里塞医院食物的症状
That's a symptom of trying to cram hospitalabcfood down a throat he can barely get air down.
瘦不是症状abc可要是毒素一年前就储藏在脂肪细胞里
It's not a symptom, but what if theabctoxins were stored in his fat cells a year ago,
现在释放进血液中
and now they're beingabcreleased into his bloodstream?
你从哪里找旧颜料?
So where you gonna get this old paint?
垃圾堆?
City dump?
从他的画中
On his old paintings.
他几年来都没卖出过画
We know he hasn't sold one in ages.
但画室里找不到几幅abc他藏起来了
But there weren't many in hisabcstudio. He's hid them somewhere.
要是你错了
If you're wrong...
他随时可能因为romano-ward综合症猝死abc你清楚么?
he could drop dead from romano-wardabcat any moment. You okay with that?
只要给我几个小时
Just give me a few hours.
你有一个小时
You got one.
我需要和他单独谈谈
I need to talk to him alone.
关于你的工作 画
It's about your work. Your paintings.
我要看你最近卖出的所有画作
I need to look at all theabcones you've sold recently.
亲爱的 让我们单独谈吧
Honey, can you give us a minute?
单独谈你的画?
To talk about your paintings?
Brandon 告诉我发生了什么事
Brandon, please. Tellabcme what's going on.
我在过去三年只卖出了两幅画
I've only sold two paintings inabcthe last... three years.
自从我们认识
Since we met.
一幅还是卖给表哥
One was to my cousin.
我靠参加药物试验挣钱
I've been makingabcmoney enrolling in drug trials.
一次两种 三种药
Two, three at a time.
为什么骗我?
Why did you lie to me?
我想成为...
I wanna be, uh...
你眼中的我 你让我感受到的自己
the way you look at me.abcThe way it makes me feel.
我想成为...你看到的我
Uh, I wanna be... what you see...
当你注视着我
when you look at me.
你觉得我这么肤浅?
You think I'm that shallow?
当我注视你 我看到的是你
When I look at you... I see you.
那么
So...
你没卖掉的画放在哪里?
where are the ones you didn't sell?
不是颜料 是药物
It's not the paint,it's the drugs.
他没有用药
He's not on the drugs.
是很难理解abc但我看到了他最近六个月的画
I know it doesn't make sense, but I'm lookingabcat his paintings for the last six months.
四月 六月 八月是正常的
They're normal april, june, and august.
五月 七月 九月扭曲了
But they're distorted may,abcjuly, september.
每隔一个月 他视觉失认就会发作
Every other month,he wasabchaving visual agnosia,
因为每隔一个月 他就同时用三种药物
because every other month he wasabcon all three drugs simultaneously.
症状就是一个月出现 一个月消失
The statin was oneabcmonth on,one month off.
我不知道为什么会一时有一时无abc但确实是由于药物
I don't know why the symptoms keepabccoming and going, but it is the drugs.
藏在楼梯下
They're hiding under the stairs.
在脂肪里? 不会
In the fat? That doesn't make sense.
药物是不溶于脂肪的
These drugs aren't fat soluble.
我说的是楼梯 不是壁橱
I said stairs,not closet.
在他症状发作时用的药之前abc他用的是什么药?
What was the last drug he was on before theabcdrugs he was on when the symptoms started?
不知道
I'm not sure.I think--
抗酸剂
antacid.
- 你怎么知道?abc- 这合乎逻辑么
- How do you know?abc- It makes sense.
何况我看着档案呢
Also, I'm looking at the file.
怎么?
Yes?
House医生打来的
It's dr. House.
叫醒他吧 准备好了
Uh, wake him up. We're done.
不 他说需要做手术abc不是这个
No, no--he says he needsabcsurgery, but not this one.
他有说具体的吗?
Did he give any specifics?
腹部手术去除一块毛粪石
Abdominal surgery to remove A... bezoar.
像是一块毛团 由未消化的食物堆积而成
It's like a hairball, butabcit's made up of undigested food.
胃酸过少的话 就可能形成abcBrandon恰因用试验性抗酸剂而胃酸不足
You can get it if your stomach acid's low, whichabcbrandon's was because of an experimental antacid.
水果 蔬菜的纤维和皮黏在一起abc形成一个球
Fruit and vegetable fibers and skinsabcget stuck together and form a ball.
黏糊糊的 发酵 不断变大
It gets sticky,ferments, grows.
他服下的药物有些也被包裹进球里
It starts sucking up someabcof the pills he'd taken.
有些药没有发挥药效
Some are never heard from again.
但有些释放了
But some get released.
上周 很大剂量的三种药物同时作用
For the last week,it's basically beenabcgiving him massive doses of all three at once.
瞧这个...
And that...
就是为什么我不让Cameron养猫的原因
is why I won't let cameron buy a cat.
他会好起来的
He should be fine.
他告诉你真相 你高兴吗?
Are you glad he told you the truth?
是的 当然
Yes... of course.
但...
But...
比不知道前更高兴吗?
were you happier before you knew?
还有10步
About ten more feet.
我知道它长什么样abc就不用蒙眼睛了吧
I do know what it looks like, soabcmaybe this whole blindfold thing--
我买礼物 我说了算abc小心地上
shh--my gift,abcmy rules. Bump.
要是颜色你不喜欢 可以改abc不过我希望
All right, if you don'tabclike the cabut I'm hoping.
准备好了?
You ready?
喜欢吗?
Do you like it?
宝贝 你没事吧?
Baby, are you okay?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
她不相信
*****
该死
Damn.
那你啥也没得到
So you didn't get anything.
没
Nothin'.
我们大概做过头了
We probably overstepped.
你确实不像啦啦队的
You're really not the cheerleader type.
除此之外
On the other hand,
我想她也不信我会伪造相片
I figured she probably wouldn't figureabcme as the "photoshopping" a photo
拼接在年久黯淡的大学报刊上
and planting it in an obscureabccollege paper "type either.
关于这个
Heh, yeah. About that.
我小游一番你的母校
I took a little trip to your alma mater.
150英里算小游
You took a little trip 150 miles.
在线游览 打电话
Online, by phone.
我意思是做了调查
I meant I did research.
这是张真相片 对吧?
That's a real photo,isn't it?
哇 真够丢人
Wow, that is humiliating.
有个姑娘
There was a girl.
不止
Even more so.
太糟糕了
That's too bad.
你希望她从新的角度看你 可...
You wanted her to see you inabca different light, and...
她不仅没有看到
not only didn't she see it...
她压根不信有这个可能
she didn't even believe it was possible.
随意给人编排理论的人abc最招人讨厌
You know,people hate peopleabcwho have theories about people.
想我停手?
You want me to back off?
你会吗?
Would you?
我还完全不了解你呢
I barely know you.